Diego Cattaneo

Frontend Developer Buenos Aires, Argentina

diegocattaneo@hotmail.com.ar	\ +54 9 11 2251 8731	<u>dcattaneo.vercel.app</u>	github.com/dcattaneo

As a frontend developer with more than 2 years experience working with React and Typescript, and some backend skills using Node.js, I enjoy creating quality products to provide a good user experience, following best practices, which are essential for writing efficient, clean and reusable code.

Experience

Frontend Developer - Instituto Nacional de Tecnología Industrial (INTI)

Jan 2023 - Present

- I have worked with the team in the redesign and rebuild of the web application, as well as in its ongoing maintenance and improvement.
- Collaborating on user experience improvements in order to increase their engagement.
- Web Developer Freelance

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022

• Custom websites developed for clients as a freelancer using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and non-relational databases according to their needs.

Education

Degree in Computer Science - UBA

Jan 2018 - Present

Languages

- Spanish
- English

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React

- Typescript
- Tailwind
- Git
- Context API

- Node
- Express
- Mongo
- MySQL